Revenue Bird
So boring!
If you want to see it, go to buy it!
I will buy it if I have enough money.
Hi, Nobita!
Why are you napping here?
Thanks for coming!
I've bought 10 new publishing books!
Ah, you bought 10 books, Suneo?
I won't lend it to you to read.
I bought it with my pocket money.
I think men must live equally.
Don't we have no ideas to
change this wrong world?
It's really too unfair!
Suneo always enjoys the privilege.
Yet we still have some ways
that can make people live equally.
Revenue Bird
We can gather tax from the pocket money.
For example,
your have 500 Yen pocket money.
It'll take 50 Yen from it.
No jokes! I'm troublesome for
I haven't enough money to use.
But more money, more tax!
If the money is over 1 thousand,
the tax rate will be 3 percent.
And if it's over 10 thousand,
the tax rate will be 7 percent.
Thus will be a little bit fair.
And then use the collecting revenue
to buy something useful to us.
It must be decided by we all.
The problem is
whether everyone will agree.
Go to discuss with everyone.
We've never heard so good idea,
have we, everyone?
Nobita, you're so smart.
Use the revenue to make uniform
of Gian's team.
And
build an appropriative baseball ground.
And form a baseball team,
Furthermore, set up a building.
Inside there're some restaurants,
electronic playrooms, resting rooms.
And we can pull the pin.
You did go too much!
Actually you don't need to do that.
Buy whatever you would like to buy,
everyone!
I hope you can use them freely.
Shut up! I agree, okay?
Everyone is happy and agree to it.
So let's do it!
Now it's checking the pocket money
of everyone.
Doraemon, you have 100 Yen.
So you shall pay 10 Yen.
I did expect to buy Rice Cracker with it
Here is you change, 90 Yen!
It's well enough that
I have no money with me now.
What're you saying?
Now we'll go to your homes
and take the money from
your saving box as the revenue.
That's the way to my home!
Hey, wait! Don't go there!
Oh, my saving box!
There're 23,046 Yen in all!
The revenue is 16,132 Yen.
Oh, no! That's all of mine!
Thank you!
It's collecting the revenue strictly.
It seems can collect lots of money.
I've spent my deposit money
and pocket money earlier,
so I can take it easy!
I'm back!
Welcome back! Here is your
pocket money of this month, 500 Yen!
But you don't need to
give it to me at this moment.
Revenue
I'll pay! I'll pay for it, okay?
This is strict indeed!
Hi!
Uncle Nobi!
I'll go to Indian again.
And I'll stay there about 3 years!
So I'll give you gifts of money
of 3 years in advance.
Here you are!
30 thousand Yen!
I won't take it...
Oh? It's not you work-style!
Just take it!
Bye, we can't see each other
for a while. Take care!
Wait, Uncle!
You don't need to give me money!
It's okay that you have such thought.
Revenue 11,100 Yen!
How is the revenue collecting going on?
Nobita, 22,500 Yen
Shizuka, 11,200 Yen
Desuki, 49,000 Yen
Liu, 90,148 Yen
Goda Gian, None
Honekawa Suneo, None
Suneo and Gian have no money?
So that means...
Let's have a research!
First, send off the finder!
Then watch on TV!
So we don't need pocket money at all!
Is that cartoon? Let me have a read!
How is it going on where Suneo is?
Mom, do you want me to buy something?
No, nothing!
Didn't I bring you
all the deposit money just now?
Please take the money from it.
I hope you ask me to buy the
exercise necessaries with it.
I'll give it to mom
after I bought it home.
And it'll be good
if mom give it back to me!
Revenue Bird
Go to find Suneo for the revenue!
Except the pocket money,
you can't ask him for revenue!
Oh, you can't!
Oh, it's so heavy!
That's what mom asked me to buy!
Isn't the revenue too high?
You're too much!
I saved those money so hard for
I was eager to buy a microscope.
And I even went to teach
the neighbor's children in spare time.
Because saving money is my fun!
I didn't even go it on something
I wanted to buy.
We can't stop Revenue Bird!
Hey, have you collected lots of revenues
Can we buy something now?
10 Yen, it's great!
One percent of the revenue is 1 Yen!
Take it out quickly!
Bastard!
Go and ask for it from the richer men!
Great! The machine can't work, so the
game of collecting revenues is over!
Too great...
Weather Cushion!
Now it's time to broadcast the news
about children!
Today we'll go to see
what games will the children in Tokyo
play in cold weather?
Mr. Santen!
Okay, I'm Mr. Santen!
Everyone, please look here!
I believe everyone can see that
our lively little friends
are kicking up a din!
Let me interview these little friends!
Don't you feel cold?
No, we don't!
You're in high spirits!
Such extent of cold is
a piece of cake to us!
Wow, you're great!
$0 you?
You don't feel cold?
Circumfused by
the spirited little friends,
I feel my body gets warmer and warmer.
Here above is play-by-play story
of the locale.
Well, I'll invite Nobita to
go outside to play.
Nobita
What's the matter, Doraemon?
Don't keep staying at home!
You'd go outside to play sometimes.
Though I'd like to say that to you,
you won't go, right?
Because it's cold outside.
You know my thoughts so well.
Anyway, it's no funny to go outside.
It'll be bad if we have a cold.
But it'll be something else again
if it snows.
If it snows,
you'll go outside to play, will you?
Well, if so...
Machine can awake snow
Weather Cushion!
This is the textbook for the students
in the future world.
It can experience snow or wind
and all kinds of other stuffs.
For example,
if you press button Windy No. 1!
There will be high and low
air pressure places on the cushion
It'll cause the air flowing!
Really!
And if you
press the button of clouds next,
I know,
the vapor in the air will cool down
and change to small waterdrop.
And they'll gather to be clouds.
While you press the button of raining,
the waterdrops inside the bank of clouds
will get bigger and heavier and drop!
What're you doing?
The water drops to the ground.
Oh, bad!
Let's go outside to
do the experiment a while later.
Perhaps it'll thunder too!
Line up the cushions!
And broaden the area!
What kinds of snow do you like?
Of course white and thick snow it is!
If you want to ski,
then it's better to be thin.
And if you want to pile snowman,
then stretches of snow will be better.
So,
stretches of snow!
I know!
Rain will change to snow while
in lower temperature!
Yeah!
It seems hard to snow.
Doraemon, when can we pile snowman
About 20 or 30 minutes later!
Well, then call me when it snows!
Hey, it's already snowed!
Okay!
I'll pile a big snowman!
Do your best!
Hah, so it is!
Oh, so cold!
Doraemon
I have a strange question to ask.
Though you have good abilities,
you can't turn the snow warm, right?
I'll help you whatever trouble you have!
It should be laid nearby!
Found it!
There're all kinds of disks! Use this!
Oh, so warm!
The temperature
makes me feel comfortable!
So heavy!
Couldn't I pile a snowman
without others help?
Don't go too far! What am I here for...
Leave you alone! Do it by yourself?
A robot would go on the bend too!
It's shameful!
He lost the disks here!
What! How could it be?
What! Just a part of it!
Thus is relaxed! Really good!
There're many kinds of disks!
White snow! Its pronunciation
in Japanese sounds like castle's!
Originally, snow is white!
Just make it snowing to have a look!
Strange!
So-called white snow
is the castle in fact!
Snow-ball-snow!
Aren't they the snow-balls
used to play snow-battle?
Let's invite Nobita to go together!
But the brat must be in his warm home!
Gian, you look! Does Nobita
have such stuffs in his home?
What stuffs?
Strange! Isn't that a castle?
Yeah, and it's made of snow!
Nobita, where is the castle from?
I made it!
Yeah, let's play a snow-battle!
What
Okay, let's play!
Well, I made lots of snow-balls.
We can almost begin!
OK
Well, let's begin!
I won't be hit by Nobita's snow-ball!
I won't...
Run away quickly...
Great! I won Gian!
Nobita, you're great!
This is the last sheet of clouds!
Women Snow!
This seems interesting!
Why hasn't he come in yet?
Isn't it matter?
Nobita is so enjoying himself outside
that he'd not like to come in! It's rare
Help... Doraemon
Snow-girl is chasing me!
Let's play the game together!
Change to clouds?
Doraemon, you'd help me
with my homework on occasion.
I can't do that!
Clouds in the guy can fly leisurely,
that's great!
Geez! I can't stand...
Oh, you are noisy!
What! Do you still think
it's no matter with you?
Can't help!
You seem get along with your homework
slowly! Would you like to have a rest?
To have a rest... What to do?
Didn't you want to be clouds?
If I could, I'd like to be clouds.
What's that?
It's a funnel which can make people
into smoke!
It's a machine
that can float in the sky leisurely!
How can I use it?
Just have it on your head! That's okay!
Though you can change into
the shape which you'd like to be,
you can't frighten others!
I know!
You can keep this shape only for a
while! You must come back soon!
Okay!
It's a nice day today! It's good time to
practicing pronunciation.
So I'll begin!
DO RE MI...
Oh, noisy! We're taking a nap now!
It's Gian, that bastard!
Yeah, let me frighten him!
Strange!
Oh, shit!
I'm sorry to frighten you!
I'm so sorry!
What stuff are you?
You guy! Get back into shape!
Don't run...
Where did he run to?
What! Oh, it's Doraemon!
Do you see something strange?
No!
A pile of strange clouds!
Where did Nobita go?
You said that's Nobita, did you?
Nobita must have
done something wrong to Gian!
It's bad now!
What's bad?
Isn't that pile of clouds Nobita?
Oh, I don't sure.
That pile of clouds almost made me fall
down from the roof! And I almost died.
Doraemon... Help me! Doraemon
Mom, do you know where Doraemon go
Doraemon'? He went out just now.
Lots of smoke!
Oh, no, mom! You can't!
Nobita, what's wrong with you?
I wouldn't like to be smoke all my life.
Doraemon
Where did you go?
I'm sorry...
Great! Got back into shape!
That...
Doraemon, what's wrong with you?
Gian
Doraemon
Didn't you promise to me
that you wouldn't play tricks?
Oh, it's used in that way!
This is good!
You must keep the promise!
You can't play tricks, understand?
Certainly I'll play tricks. That's why
I'm looking forward to being smoke.]
Geez!
What shape to change into?
Okay, that's it!
Scissors, rock, cloth
It's good to play!
Seems delicious!
Ghost...
Delicious...
Oh, that's Shizuka! She's doing homework!
Keep the answers in your mind in secret!
Strange! Suneo isn't here! Boring!
It's his diary! Someday...
My lovely citizens, big news!
Suneo had a bed-wetting last night!
There's some smoke which shape is mouth.
I've saw such big smoke!
His practical joke is too much!
We must stop him ASAP!
Gian, get back into shape!
Ouch...
What's wrong with you, my little boy?
My plane was taken away by smoke ashes.
Where is the smoke?
It's there!
There's nothing I can't do!
I'm the king!
Hey, Doraemon, Nobita!
I'll get back into shape!
Lend me that funnel!
You finally become convinced!
The black smoke ashes are still
on the body.
What to do, Doraemon?
Do something!
Please!
Hypnosis Glasses!
You eyelid gets heavier and heavier!
Get heavier and heavier!
Stand up silently!
You must stand up!
You become a stick!
Even someone sits above,
you won't feel surprised!
Oh, there're many butterflies
flying here!
You become a butterfly and begin to fly!
Butterfly... I'm butterfly!
Here is the end of the Hypnosis Unit!
Wow, so great!
Great indeed! I want to try too!
Impossible! Gian, how could you?
Yeah...
What're you saying? You two, sit down!
Yeah, so it is...
You'll feel your eyelid
get heavier and heavier.
Heavier and heavier...
Yeah, a little...
Unbend your arms!
Your arms are getting heavier and
heavier!
Not heavy at all!
Oh, you're so great!
My arms are getting so heavy
and droop slowly. So great!
Good, so good...
Here is in the sea!
Begin to swim...
Yeah, so is it...
Seems like a fool!
Hey, Nobita!
How can you be in such manner?
You bastard!
I'll teach you a good lesson!
Just pretend for a while as his will.
Help!
I'll hit you till you are
hypnosigenesised by me.
He escaped!
Nobita, what's wrong with you?
Again pushed around by Gian?
Yeah, he wanted to hypnosigenesis me,
and I didn't agree so he got angry.
Of course he couldn't do that to you!
Because learning hypnosis
is a very difficult thing.
But it'll be something else again
if you use this!
Hypnosis Glasses!
Wear this pair of glasses and speak,
that's okay!
I'll start!
You'll feel your head getting heavier!
Oh, so heavy!
Easily, I am hypnosigenesised!
Wow, so great!
Have this, anyone can
be hypnosigenesised easily!
Stop!
Nobita, have you finished your homework?
You can't go out to play!
What're you doing?
Wearing a pair of strange glasses!
Mom is going to
give pocket money to Nobita!
Here you are!
Oh, I can get the
pocket money again! It's useful!
You brat!
Ready to die!
Don't be so violent, please!
What?! You asked me not to be so violent
Okay, I won't use violence!
He's hypnosigenesised!
Wow, he's so great!
Gian is a gentel girl!
Yeah, I am a girl!
Nobita, let's play together, shall we?
I'm busy now. Let's play next time!
Bye-bye!
Oh, it's Shizuka and others!
They're playing skipping!
I want to join them!
Can I join in?
Of course you can!
But what's wrong with you, Gian?
Do you really want to play skipping?
Let's play together!
What's wrong with Gian?
What's Gian doing now?
You bastard!
He appears!
You guy!
You are dog?!
Dog...
Why have I done as Nobita's requirement?
Didn't you hypnosigenesised by him?
Hypnosigenesised?
Yeah!
Bunged your ears!
So that you won't hear
what Nobita says. So what?
Well, I'll try in this way!
Nobita, I'll teach you a good lesson!
Don't you see me?
This time I become a bird
and fly to somewhere else.
Become a bird...
Because I bunged my ears!
What
You bastard!
I'll teach you a good lesson!
Nobita, stay here...
I told you stay here.
Help!
How to do...
I really don't know what to do with you.
Stand in front of the mirror and
hypnosigenesis yourself!
Oh, I see! So it is!
Just as the idea
in Doraemon's mind,
I'm in hypnosis and
become a wrestling player.
Yeah!
What a pair of unusual sunglasses!
Looks like a owl!
Owl?
Nobita, do you know where dad is?
You don't know, right?
Perhaps he went to buy cigarette.
Geez! Dinner is ready!
Dad is really troublesome!
Nobita, go outside to look for it!
There's a good programme on show now.
Doraemon, go to find it!
Chocolate of heart shape!
Everyone, be careful to defend!
Hit a nice ball!
Just throw the ball!
Oh, such strange ball!
I'm sure to a home run!
Nobita isn't able to hit my ball!
Just see it if you don't believe!
Nice ball!
What're you laughing?
Well, Nobita, it's my turn!
But I...
Do you have any question?
No...
Gian, no, you can't.
Why
Because all could play by turns.
Yes.
You jumped the queue, you go to far.
If you want to play, you could line the
last.
Stop, you didn't obey me,
You guy! I am anger.
Stop...
Don't run.
How terrible!
How violent!
If only Gian appear, whatever
game will be mixed it
But if we don't agree him, him
will revenge, it is terrible.
But...
we must be trifled by him always?
I know your mean, but his power is big.
Yes.
Well...
Let us edge out him together.
We won't say hello with him
when we meet him on the way.
If he ask us something, we don't care
him.
OK...
It's good idea, let us do it.
OK, we make a appointment
that we won't pay attention to Gian
I agree.
Yes, return back
if we don't pay attention to Gian,
it will be fine.
Yes, we don't pay attention to him,
Gian is just a kid.
Yes, how about me?
Gian
What did you say about me?
Nothing, we said that Gian is a good
man.
Yes... you are manful.
Really, ok.
Mama ask me go to buy something.
You help me.
It just a little thing, we go at once.
What, I haven't feared already.
Gian the guy is kid,
I don't pay attention to him.
Gian, sorry, please forgive me.
What did you say?
It's Nobita's idea.
He said that Gian is a monster.
No, he said that let's edge out you.
What? Edge me?
Nobita, that guy!
I don't know, I didn't say it.
I don't know this case.
Stop... I ask you stop.
I won't pay attention to Gian,
absolutely
Nobita, I ask you stop, you guy!
What, all betrayed you.
Yes.
Yes, it is, I couldn't bear it.
OK, in this case, you use it.
Heart style of chocolate
You spare it to all, all idea will
same as yours.
The idea the first ate will pass all.
Make all idea is same.
Oh, I see. Good.
Chocolate.
Please have some one.
Although I have enough
If you entertain, I will eat.
Nobita entertain all eat chocolate.
Yes, it's rare.
Do you want? The chocolate is delicious.
Please, thank you.
Aunty, please. Thank you.
Uncle, please.
Thank you.
Please eat chocolate. Thank you.
Here you are.
Good...
So, all idea will same.
Vive!
All edge out Gian!
Wait!
Why must we buy something for Gian?
I am anger when I think more.
I am anger more and more.
Thank you...
Please give me.
What is it?
What are you doing, don't run.
Shit
Why are they, up to them.
Suneo, you...
What are you doing... hey...
You guy, don't run.
Ouch!
Ouch...
Stop, what are you doing, stop!
Cheap of it.
So I feel fine.
Shizuka
If I hope the idea of all of the
world is same
the world will be peace.
Really?
Yes.
But if most ideas are same
I will feel strange.
Really?
Shizuka
Who? Strange.
I want to meet Shizuka
Me too.
Shit, all have eaten the chocolate.
All ideas are same as me.
Look, the station will develop like this
As if we couldn't do it.
Save Xhei
Xhei has grown up.
Have you found it already?
You are thorough. Rear hexapod
it is rare for you.
At times, you should let it take a walk.
You go.
Xhei looks like happy.
Nobita, what are you doing.
Hi, Shizuka
What a big unicorn
It calls Xhei
How big. Where did you buy?
I rear it since it was younger.
Its power is strange.
Nobita
The unicorn you rear is nice.
Lend me it and have a look.
No.
Just a while, couldn't you agree?
I see. OK.
I will return you at post office of
Hengding Street after 30 minutes.
Hey, Nobita, he won't return you.
Lend' in Gian's mind is 'present'
No. He can't.
He come here.
Nobita, do you wait for a long time?
Where is my Xhei
He has run away.
Run away?
It is my first time that I know unicorn
has wing.
He has 'ba da ba da' flown
You lie, definitely
Gian, don't lie, return Xhei to me.
What? Do you doubt me?
You have agreed, it's your fault.
You may rear other.
Shizuka, you don't know, there
is only a Xhei in the world.
Nobita...
How come, Doraemon
You look downhearted, I give you a
funny game.
Thank you, but it is useless.
Don't say it like this.
You speak to hexapod canister
Hexapod canister
It calls Worm Transaudient Canister
Worm Transaudient Canister
You try.
OK, let me try.
Dragonfly, stop at this finger.
It stopped.
You could speak with it.
Ant go forward, there are some
cookie on the ground.
I could speak to ant.
How come?
It's weird.
But how about Xhei now?
Nobita
I found it.
What, Gian made Xhei...
Yes, I have found it.
He is playing well.
Move faster
If you are draggy, I will pull you.
How come?
It is just small, you couldn't pull it.
You are my joss.
Gian, your friend is visiting you.
Hi, Nobita
What do you ask me?
Return Xhei to me.
You doubt me yet,
I have told you it has run away.
But someone told me that you take it.
Don't speak more.
Well, I have a good way.
Use Worm Transaudient Canister and
ask ant to research burrow for us.
Could I do?
You wait and see.
Ant, I am counting on you.
They come back.
They have drawn the map of Gian's room
As if Xhei is on the table.
But Gian set at the table
How to save Xhei
If you use Worm Transaudient
Canister, it won't have any question.
What's wrong...
All stop on my ice-cream.
You don't run...
Stop.
How slower.
What happened?
Nobita, the ant said that they can't
move Xhei because it is weighty.
What should we do?
Well, in this case, I ask big
hexapod of Gian's house.
The big hexapod of Gian's house,
please save Xhei
Doraemon, is it okay?
I don't know, we only could wait.
Cockroach have moved out Xhei
Cockroach, thank you.
Xhei, good.
Who is there?
He found it, hurry to run away.
Hurry to run away...
They guys are faster.
Hey, follow smell
If I find you, you will repent
He found us.
I won't let you run away again.
How terrible...
Flea, hurry to help us.
What's wrong...
I feel itchy
How itchy...
Look, Gian he ran away.
Doraemon, please ask flea
let Gian pass
Wait 30 minutes and see.
Change Opinion Gun
Nobita, what are you doing.
You will know after you look.
It is hexapod sample.
What is it?
Oh, don't you know?
Take hold of lucanidae, unicorn or
cigala
and put in this box
You want to ask me bring out
catch hexapod machine again
You don't worry.
If you have it, you could all.
Please continue.
Good bye, I go.
It is goldbug, it is aphis.
I have caught more, let's go home.
Okay.
Brother, have you caught more hexapod?
Only child play this game about
catch cigala, I don't play it.
Because we catch hold of flying cigalas
they will be poor.
But you have caught them, it is nothing
We may release them later.
I couldn't catch hold of one, Mechanical
Cat will make fun of me.
Well, I have a good way.
Put a clean paper in empty box
Like this, put it here, it is okay.
Then, what will you do?
I will make a grot of cigala
What, a grot of cigala?
Yes, cigala will nidify in it.
Then cigala will be more and
here are cigalas all around.
It's normal
You are incurable.
Do you know?
If cigala spawn on the ground,
larva will live on the ground
Really?
Yes.
The station larva grow, child know it.
I will tell all, so all will make fun
of you.
No...
Suneo
Offtime machine for a while
Anyway, we prohibit him first,
then we find a way to settle it.
Please, I don't want to be make fun of
all.
Especial Shizuka, I don't know
how to do if she know it.
You are loud.
I am thinking, please be quiet.
Let us use it.
Change Opinion Gun
You needn't kill him.
No, I just make a test
If I say that is a cat, what will you
think?
I say you are a idiot.
It's just a cat.
Don't joke, hurry to find a way.
You watch carefully. Now matter
how to watch, it is just a cat.
How foolish.
But it is a cat really.
So...
This is a dog.
What, you said the cat was a dog.
You couldn't know what is dog. Jeez.
Look, I am right.
It's impossible.
No matter I am foolish, dog is dog.
Okay, I ask other.
Excuse me, is it a dog?
You are a student of primary school,
you should know what is dog or cat.
It's cat.
Yes... that is a cat.
No, it is dog.
You, it mew just now.
Because it touched
the light the gun shot out
Whatever, its mind will same as me.
So you shot at them just now, didn't
you?
Hey, you should tell me early.
Suneo, you could move.
Strange, what did I do just now?
Right, I wanted to tell Shizuka this
case.
Shit, I don't hope Shizuka know it.
Hurry to go there, okay.
Shizuka, please listen me, Nobita he...
Hurry to shoot at Shizuka
It is funny, isn't it?
It's normal.
Because cigala nidify in the tree,
it is a matter of course.
All know it.
You lie, it is impossible.
You are bad-manner, I didn't lie.
How strange.
But Shizuka, she shouldn't lie.
Yes, but cigala nidify in the tree...
Well, Gian's skill is high, let me ask
Gian
We must get there early than he.
What, please tell me your question.
I could tell you all.
Cigala spawn on the ground, right?
Shoot at Gian
I'm wrong, you are foolish.
Cigala spawn in the grot and hatch
What, hatch?
Suneo, is it enough like this?
I could tell you more.
OK, I will ask mama the truth.
Suneo, you are stubborn.
I am tired.
Mama, listen to me.
Cigala spawn on the ground, right?
Yes or no, mama
Why did you ask this question easily.
Don't care more, hurry to tell me.
Cigala nidify and spawn in the tree,
then hatch
It is a matter of course. You are
shameful.
If you study halfheartedly, it will
troublesome.
No, I am right.
If cigala know hatch, I make a test.
What should I do, I have no way,
shoot at cigala.
It couldn't be.
Larva has hatched on 7
Cigala's parent gnaw food and fledge
larva. Larvas mew.
Strange.
The money hasn't enough.
I want it.
1800 Yen.
It is expensive.
And saving box is empty.
What is wrong?
You are my best friend, aren't you?
Why did you speak it like this now?
Actually...
What... please tell me.
It is that...
Make money machine.
What the heck are you talking about?
Why do I have that machine?
You needn't anger.
Listen, you make money
licentiously, it is illegal.
Will it same in the future.
Yes.
Well, about make money way
Well, discuss with dad
I know you will say it.
Well, I tell you a good way
You thrum my back every day,
I will pay you 10 Yen.
Every day.
So I will store up 300 Yen for a month.
I will store up 1800 Yen for half of
year
Half of year
I want to get it now.
Stop.
You unearned idea is bed.
You should know it has fun when you
work.
Even time is half year, you should
buy it by yourself.
I think you will happy by then.
I will be happy if I could buy it now.
As if he don't know what dad said.
I bought it, what do you think?
Let me see.
It is the top-drawer made in foreign
soil
It must be expensive.
Yes.
Brother in law could buy one.
I couldn't buy it.
I didn't feel funny to play outside.
Hi, uncle.
Hey, will you buy that car together?
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
You salary is little, but you bought
the expensive goods.
On installment
Then you should pay
I take it first, then I enjoy it as I
Pay-.
It is modern life
Modern life...
Good bye.
This is good.
What?
Modern life.
How comfortable
If it like dad's word that you
should bear half of year.
Yes.
You must keep doing it
Okay.
You are cool, I should reappraise you
You must bear half of year.
No.
I will take it at once.
How to take it?
Use it...
Use time machine
I will have 1800 Yen after half of
year.
I don't know.
Nothing, I only use my saving.
Will it be well-Off?
Here is my room like this after half of
year.
Because it is morning, I should in
school after half of year.
I put the saving box there always,
but it disappear
Doraemon, please look for it for
me.
You also dislike keeping
neatness after half of year.
Did you change place?
It's your fault that you heave around.
Mama, did you see my saving box?
No.
Nobita, why didn't go to school?
Shit.
Stop.
Doraemon, did you see Nobita?
No.
It's troublesome.
It's saving box.
Oh, I hid it here.
It is 10 Yen coin, total is 1800 Yen.
You have saved more.
Anyway, hurry to go back and buy toy.
Let's go.
You are me after half of year.
Yes.
I found my saving of half of year
disappear when I came back.
In order to reach here early than you,
I ridded time machine.
You return my saving.
Don't speak what I should remand.
We are same, please clam down and sit
down.
This money is my saving.
No.
The man who deposit money is me.
During half of year, I thrum dad's
back every day.
Do you know I am so toilful?
The man is me. I am toilful.
But you are me.
No, although you are me...
I mix.
Anyway, you should return my saving.
I don't care you.
Ratfink.
Nobita, don't run.
Stop.
You must put to right.
What?
The man who messed up isn't me.
Bought it...
Sure, sure enough, it has changed like
this
I have forecasted it.
You wait, you will be repentant.
No.
Hurry to assembled. Okay.
You are wrong, not it.
What are you doing'? It is fine like
this.
No, it isn't, the sections should be
Well, you could leave this part to me.
You don't know how to assembled at all,
but you want to do, you are strange.
You assembled wrong.
No, the man is you, you are wrong.
You should use this sections.
You don't know how to assembled at all.
All go to bits.
1800 Yen go bang.
Nobita, you should thrum dad's
back every day, right?
I have given up.
Nobita, why did you give plan up on
mid-way?
It is wrong like this.
Brother-in-law, only once, please lend
me money.
Because I should refund, but my
saving isn't enough.
Please lend me some money.
Modern life is toilful.
Please...
Look, he flower and the grass
Every one
So we walk happily
And sing happily
We are human
Planet in the university
It is the country full of dreams and
smile faces
We walk together
We are human being
Today or tomorrow or the day after
tomorrow
We create together
The city full of dreams